Social Welfare, School of; Records ua690
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1964-1999; Undated; 5; 7 cubic ft.
  - Social Work Practice Conferences, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Social Work Program Rankings - Articles and Reports, 1990; 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9-10)
  - Social Work Research Development Center Follow-Up, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Social Work Research Development Center Follow-Up Letter to Ellen Stover, 1996; 1998; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Social Work Research Development Center Grant Proposal, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Social Work Research Development Center Seed Infrastructure Funding Proposal, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Social Work Research Development Center Thornberry Grant, 1996-1997 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Strategic Planning, 1969; 1989-1991; 1995; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17-19)
  - Strategic Plan Reports and Findings, 1990-1994; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - 1996 Student Awards, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Student Grievance Committee Meeting Minutes, 1981; 1989 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Student Grievance Committee Members, 1980-1988; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Student Grievance Committee Operating Procedures, 1980-1981; 1983; 1988 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Student Grievance Committee - Student Grievance Reports - [RESTRICTED], 1980-1984; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Student Standing Committee Communications - [RESTRICTED], 1984-1889; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Student Standing Committee Members, 1980-1987; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Student Standing Committee Meeting Minutes - [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Survey of the Community Service Program, 1976 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - SUNY/Higher Education Data, 1989-1993; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - 1989 - 1990 Albany Data, Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Undergraduate Academic Council - [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Undergraduate Alumni Survey, 1980-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Undergraduate Majors List, 1989-1991 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Undergraduate Program Committee Meeting Minutes and Communications, 1988; 1990-1991; 1994; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Undergraduate Program Curriculum Revision, 1996-1997 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Undergraduate Social Welfare Program, 1976; 1989-1991; 1992-1994; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Undergraduate Who's Who Among Students, 1989-1990; 1993-1994 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - University Presidential Inauguration - Patrick Swygert, 1991; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - University/Regional Interaction Inventory, 1976 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Voluntary Action Center of Albany, 1973 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Walter M. Beattie Jr. Award, 1987; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
- Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications, 1973-1990; Undated; 6; 5.2 cubic ft.
  Publications within this series are products of the Continuing Education Program (CEP). These publications represent a major function of the CEP through its development of instructional resources for use in social welfare agencies and educational institutions. Topics covered within these publications include income maintenance, education, health and fitness, rehabilitation, corrections, child welfare, gerontology, staff development, public housing, employment, and industrial social work. Please see box 3 folder 16 for the Guide to Continuing Education Program Publications, which lists all publications created up until ca. 1980. This guide also contains additional information about the functions and goals of the CEP. Please note that this series contains only CEP publications; general files relating to the Continuing Education Program are located in the Subject Files series.
  - Absent Parent Training - Income Maintenance Training Institute Program Material, 1984 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1)
  - Advanced Training Program for Supervisors - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance Training, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 2)
  - Advanced Training Program for Supervisors Year II - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance Training, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 3)
  - Advanced Training Program for Workers - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance Training, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 4)
  - Advanced Training Program for Workers Year II - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance Training, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 5)
  - An Assessment of Training Priorities: Implications of the Child Welfare Reform Act, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 6)
  - Attacking the Error Rate: Strategies for Improvement - Proceedings of the Annual Corrective Action Conference, 1984 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 7)
  - Basic Adult Services: A Model Curriculum, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 8-9)
  - Basic Adult Services: A Model Curriculum, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 10)
  - Brunswick County Joins WMS, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 11)
  - Caring for Your Adult Residents, ca. 1983 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 12)
  - A Case of Reasonable Time, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 13)
  - A Caseworker's Guide to the Law of Permanency in New York State, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 14)
  - Categorical Determination for Aid to Dependent Children and Home Relief - Income Maintenance Training Institute, 1984 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 15)
  - Categorical Determination for Aid to Dependent Children and Home Relief - Income Maintenance Training Institute Case Studies, 1982-1985; Undated (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 16)
  - Child Abuse - A Teaching Guide, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 17)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect Social Services Reader I and II, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 18)
  - Childcare Training Needs Assessment, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 19)
  - Childcare Training Needs Assessment, 1980 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 20)
  - Communicating with Clients: A Reader, 1983 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 21)
  - Computers, People, and the Delivery of Services: How to Manage the Management Information System, 1977; 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 22)
  - Constructive Use of Family Court Audiotape Series, ca. 1978 (Cassette 1-5)
  - Constructive Use of Family Court: Guidelines for Using Audiotape Series, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 23)
  - Cost Control in the Medical Assistance Program, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 24)
  - Demonstrating Interviewing Skills for Income Maintenance and Medical Assistance Workers, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 25)
  - Developing Individual Employment Plans - Income Maintenance Training Institute, ca. 1984 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 26)
  - Developing Training Programs for Income Maintenance, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 27)
  - Developing Training Programs for Income Maintenance and Medical Assistance, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 28)
  - Developing Training Programs for Income Maintenance and Medical Assistance, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 29)
  - Disciplining an Employee of the Brevard County Department of Social Services, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 31)
  - A Discussion Guide to the Eligibility Interview, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 30)
  - Eligibility Calculations Under the Food Stamp Act of 1977 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 32)
  - Enhancing Employability Through Work Experience - Income Maintenance Training Institute, 1985 (Box 1 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 33)
  - Enhancing Interviewing Skills of Income Maintenance Workers, 1980 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1)
  - Enhancing Interviewing Skills of Medical Assistance Workers, 1977 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 2)
  - Enhancing Interviewing Skills of Medical Assistance Workers - A Regulation and Procedures Supplement for Trainers, 1977 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 3)
  - Enhancing Interview Skills of Income Maintenance and Medical Assistance Workers: An Assessment in Special Areas, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 4)
  - Enhancing Skills in Supervision for Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance Supervisors Vol. I, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 5)
  - Enhancing Skills in Supervision for Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance Supervisors Vol. II, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 6)
  - Family-Type Homes for Adults: Food and Nutrition, Money Management, and Individual Needs, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 7)
  - Family-Type Homes for Adults: Recruitment and Training Program Maintenance: A Training Curriculum, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 8)
  - Family-Type Homes for Adults: Social Needs, Physical Needs, and Home Safety and Management, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 9)
  - Financial Planning for In-Service Training in the Midsize Department of Social Welfare, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 10)
  - Food Stamp Curriculum Module 1: The New Food Stamp Supervisor, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 11-12)
  - Food Stamp Curriculum Module 4: The New Food Stamp Issuance Cashier, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 13-14)
  - Food Stamp Curriculum Trainer's Guide, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 15-18)
  - Food Stamp Outreach and Nutrition Education in Amalgamated County: A Non-Compliance Problem, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 19)
  - Food Stamp Regional Training - Income Maintenance Training Institute, Undated (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 20)
  - Group Formation: A Guide to the Development of Successful Groups, 1982 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 21)
  - Guide to Procedures in Financial Management, 1979 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 22)
  - Guide to the Use of Basic Adult Services - A Model Curriculum, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 23)
  - The Helping Connection: A Curriculum for Family Work in Protective Services, 1982 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 24-25)
  - Home Care Curriculum Trainee's Manual, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 26-28)
  - Home Care Curriculum Trainer's Manual, 1983 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 29-30)
  - Implementing Chap in Mohawk County, 1977 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 31)
  - Incidents From Income Maintenance and Medical Assistance Interviews: Recertification/Reapplication, 1979 (Box 2 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 32)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute Program Materials, 1981-1985 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1-5)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute Regional Employment Program, ca. 1983 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 6-7)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute Regional Food Stamp Program, ca. 1983 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 8)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute Regional Food Stamp Training - Interview Management, 1984 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 9)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute Residential Training for New IM Eligibility Workers, ca. 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 10-13)
  - Information Resources for Social Services Training, 1978 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 14)
  - Installation of a Statewide Food Stamp Program at the County Level - A Teaching Guide, 1977 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 15)
  - Instructional and Training Resources - Guide to Continuing Education Program Publications, ca. 1980 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 16)
  - Issues in Supervision and Management: Overview, 1990 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 17)
  - Journal of Continuing Social Work Education: Organizing Community and Other Resources for Social Service Staff Training, 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 18)
  - Journal of Continuing Social Work Education Vol. 5 Number 1, 1989 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 19)
  - Lee v. Smith: A Problem in Implementing A Judicial Decision, 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 20)
  - Legal Issues in Protective Services for Adults: Recommendations for Use of Videotape, 1978 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 21)
  - Management Comes to Mosaic County Welfare Department, 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 22)
  - Managing A Formula Grant Project, 1978 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 23)
  - Managing Reductions in the Work Force, 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 24)
  - Manpower Survey and Analysis, 1976 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 25)
  - Medical Aspects of Child Abuse and Neglect - Child Protective Services, 1977 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 26)
  - A Medical Assistance Crisis in Rockdale County, 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 27)
  - Meeting Community Needs: A Training Manual, 1979 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 28)
  - Meeting the Needs of Pregnant Adolescents - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance, 1980 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 29)
  - MH-9: A Case Problem in Community Participation, 1978 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 30)
  - The New Commissioner is a Manager, 1977; 1981 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 31)
  - New York State Department of Social Services AIDS Education Trainer's Guide, 1987 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 32)
  - A Non-Compliance Problem: Revision of New York State's Shelter Allowance Policy, 1977 (Box 3 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 33)
  - On the Line in Child care: An Entry Level Training Curriculum for Residential Child care, 1984 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1-2)
  - Poindexter County Insight Center, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 3)
  - Programming in Residential Child care: A Training Experience for Child care Workers, 1979 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 4)
  - Public Welfare Staff Development: A Role and Competency Framework for Curriculum Development and Instruction, 1982 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 5-8)
  - Quality Circles: A Bibliography of Selected Resources, 1982 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 9)
  - Readings in Adult Foster Care, 1979 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 10)
  - Readings in Aging and Social Work, 1979 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Reception/Intake Process in IM/MA, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 12)
  - Residential Child care: A Reader, 1978 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 13)
  - Response to Changing Demands for Foster care Services, 1977 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 14)
  - Role of the Supervisor and the Staff Developer in Preparing for Institute Attendance and Preparing for Follow-Up, ca. 1985 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 15)
  - Selected Training Program for Supervisors - Planning and Conducting Effective Meetings, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 16)
  - Selected Training Program for Supervisors - Supervisory Performance Skills, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 17)
  - Selected Training Program for Workers: Communication Skills, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 18)
  - Selected Training Program for Workers: Understanding Alcohol and Substance Abusing Clients, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 19)
  - Selected Training Topic for Workers in IM/MA - Handling Stress at Work, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 20)
  - Selecting the New Commissioner, 1981 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 21)
  - Selective Guide to the Literature on Communicating with Clients, 1983 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 22)
  - Services to the Older Adult: A Basic Reader, 1977 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 23)
  - Social Policy & Services: A Process-Oriented Reader, 1979 (Oversized 1)
  - Social Services Planning Manual, 1979 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 24)
  - The Social Work Process Teacher's Guide, 1978 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 25)
  - Sociocultural and Service Issues in Working with Afro-American Clients, 1985 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 26-27)
  - Sociocultural and Service Issues in Working with Clients with Disabilities, 1978 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 28)
  - Sociocultural and Service Issues in Working with Hispanic American Clients, 1985 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 29)
  - The Special Adoption Training Guide, ca. 1978 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 30)
  - Special Needs Programs for Supervisors - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance, 1979 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 31)
  - Special Needs Programs for Workers - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance, 1979 (Box 4 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 32)
  - Special Needs Programs - Income Maintenance/Medical Assistance, 1978 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1)
  - Staff Development Survey/Analysis, 1979 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 2)
  - Statewide Needs Assessment Survey, 1979 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 3)
  - Supervision in Child Protection, 1986 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 4-5)
  - Task Analysis in Public Welfare Staff Development - A Report on the New York City Experience, 1977 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 6-7)
  - Title IV-D Child Support Enforcement - Income Maintenance Training Institute, 1981; 1983-1984 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Title IV-D Program in New York State, 1977 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 9)
  - Title XX: Bane or Blessing for Settlement Houses, 1980 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 10)
  - Towards Collaboration in Foster care: A Training Guide, 1980 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 11)
  - Trainer's Guide to IV-A/IV-D Interface Training - Income Maintenance Training Institute, 1983 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 12)
  - Training Adult Family-Type Home Providers - A Manual, 1983 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 13)
  - Training in the Human Services: 5th Annual Conference Abstracts, 1981 (Box 5 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 14)
  - Training Program for Reception/Intake Workers Year II, 1981 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1)
  - Training Program for Supervisors - IM/MA Second Edition, 1979 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 2-3)
  - Training Program for Supervisors Year II - IM/MA, 1978 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 4)
  - Training Program for Workers - IM/MA Second Edition, 1979 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 5)
  - Training Program for Workers Year II - IM/MA, 1978 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 6)
  - Training Program Materials Appendix, ca. 1983 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 7)
  - Training Resources for Supervisors in IM/MA Second Edition, 1979 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 8)
  - Training Resources for Supervisors in IM/MA Third Edition, 1981 (Box 6 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 9)
  - Training Resources for Workers in IM/MA Second Edition, 1979 (Box 7 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 1)
  - Training Resources for Workers in IM/MA Third Edition, 1981 (Box 7 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 2)
  - Utility Disconnection Response Procedures, 1980 (Box 7 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 3)
  - Working with the Neighborhood - A New Power Base for Social Change in the 1980s, 1981 (Box 7 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 4)
  - Your Food Stamp Program in the New York State - A Trainer's Guide, 1977 (Box 7 (6-Continuing Education Program (CEP) Publications), Folder 5)
- Web Archives, 1997 June 16-2016 September 17; 7; 1041 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition